ivisits.net 2015-12-28

# iVisits.net | Best Travel Deals

If you require any more information or have any questions about our privacy policy, please feel free to contact us

Access to the iVisits.net is conditional on your acceptance of our Privacy Policy. When you log on and use our website, or a site powered by us, this implies consent to this Privacy Policy. As new and fascinating things always happen in the online world, we will update our Privacy Policy accordingly to reflect these changes. Your continued use of the website following an amendment to the Privacy Policy will confirm your acceptance of these revisions.

At iVisits.net we are committed to the protection of your personal information while you are on our site. We don’t want to collect any personal or sensitive information about you. What is personal or sensitive info? That's basically information or opinions about your health, political affiliations, sexual preferences, religious beliefs, racial or ethnic origin or other such private information.

Cookies are used for the website to send certain information to your browser and for your browser to return the information at a later time. We can use this information for things like, authenticating, or identifying a user session (such as a previous hotel search), user preference or any other function that can be completed through storing text data. This kind of function does not include information that personally identifies you.

Most browsers accept cookies automatically. Your browser may have settings so you can refuse cookies. De-activating cookies may mean that you will no longer be able to enjoy the full operational capabilities of the website and you may not be able to see information that is directly relevant to you. For you to get the most from the user experience on the iVisits.net site or a site powered by us, we collect certain information or “cookies”. What this means is that when you opt for certain preferences we assign you cookies and these are stored on your browser to give you an optimum user experience on our website. This information does not contain personally identifiable information and such as your name, address, email address or telephone number.

Our business is essentially a search engine for hotels. As such we present content and actively engage with trusted third party companies, who in turn, can present dynamic content to our users. Some of our trusted third party business partners use cookies to track when a click becomes a sale. Others use it to serve specific and targeted content. To learn more about the choices you have with this content please visit youronlinechoices.eu and aboutads.info/choices.
